#### AMBROSE OTUNDO ONSARE

#### **DETAILS**

- Address 2706 40200
  Kisii.
- **•** 0714062125
- ambroseotundo9@gm ail.com

#### Date of birth

20/08/1998

#### Place of birth

• Kisii

## Nationality

• Kenyan

#### **SKILLS**

- Microsoft Office
- Web Development
- C programming
- Computer networking
- Hardware repairing

#### **HOBBIES**

Listening to music

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English
- Kiswahili

#### **♣** PROFILE

I am a tech savvy person who is very enthusiastic about technology and has a lot of experience working with computers and providing tech support. I have a great array of skills and knowledge to tackle problems whenever they arise. This is possible as I have been on attachment at Rural Electrification and Renewable Energy cooperation in the ICT department. My dedication and smart working nature have helped me acquire good work ethics, autonomy and working under minimal supervision. I am proficient in Web Development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, Django), Linux and C programming.

#### WORKING EXPERIENCE

# Attaché at Rural Electrification and Renewable Energy cooperation, Nairobi in the ICT department

June 2021 — September 2021

- I helped troubleshoot computer and networking problems that the organization staff encountered.
- · Troubleshoot hardware issues.
- Configure software applications.
- Guide new attaches on problem solving and how to go about the daily support activities.

# Software Reviewer at U-test, Framingham, Massachusetts (Worked Remotely)

February 2018 — November 2020

- I reviewed software applications by finding bugs and offering an amicable solution for them.
- I tested new software before being released for general public use.

# Bug Bounty Hunter at Bug Crowd, San Francisco, CA ( Worked Remotely)

June 2020 — January 2021

• Tested systems and software for vulnerabilities and bugs.

### **EDUCATION**

## Information Science, Kisii University, Kisii

September 2017 — December 2021

• Completed studies and waiting to graduate in December 2021.

# KCSE, St. Joseph's Nyabigena Boys High School, Kisii

January 2013 — December 2016

· Completed my high school education

# KCPE, Nyambunwa Academy, Kisii

January 2004 — December 2012

- Y EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES
- Played Rugby in the Centre Position in High School
- COURSES

Cyber Ethical Hacking, Udemy

January 2019 — August 2019

**1** ■ REFEREES

**Dr. Namande Wekalau from Kisii University Information Science COD** wekanamande@gmail.com  $\cdot$  0723848930

Hiram Saitoti from Rural Electrification and Renewable Energy Cooperation System Administrator

hiram.saitoti@rerec.co.ke · 0726893431

Samuel Mwai from Rural Electrification and Renewable Energy Cooperation Systems Programmer

samuel.mwai@rerec.co.ke · 0728178044